# Jonah Rosenblum

Computer Science and Engineering University of Michigan

jonaher@umich.edu jonahrosenblum.com

### Research Interests

I am interested in systems research, and frequently this intersects with security. My current research revolves around building systems that are efficient, scalable, easy to use, and secure. Right now I am working on building a system for secure and efficient federated genomics analysis at a massive scale, and additionally a subarray-aware memory allocator for preventing Rowhammer attacks in DRAM.

### Education

**University of Michigan** 

Ann Arbor, MI

M.S. in Computer Science

Jan 2021-Dec 2021

**University of Michigan** 

Ann Arbor, MI

B.S. in Computer Science

Sep 2017-Dec 2020

Research Experience

Research Assistant

Ann Arbor, MI

University of Michigan

Jan 2022-Present

Project: Fast and Scalable Privacy-Preserving Federated GWAS with TEE

Research Mentor: Satish Narayanasamy

#### **Graduate Student Research Assistant**

Ann Arbor, MI

University of Michigan

Jan 2021-Dec 2021

Project: Fast and Scalable Privacy-Preserving Federated GWAS with TEE

Research Mentor: Satish Narayanasamy

## **Employment**

Google

Virtual

Software Engineering Intern

May-August 2021

Team: GCloud Infrastructure

Analyzed inversion between network and application priority for high-priority Google traffic across all clusters and identified strategies to align less latency sensitive traffic with appropriate QoS.

Virtual Google

Software Engineering Intern

May-August 2020

Team: Cloud Trace

Worked on open-source telemetry tool OpenTelemetry, implementing graceful shutdown for processes to ensure all traces and metrics are exported.

**Teaching** 

# **Parallel Computer Architecture (EECS 570)**

Graduate Student Instructor for Prof. Satish Narayanasamy

Ann Arbor, MI Jan-May 2021

## Technical Skills

Programming Languages: Very comfortable with C, C++, and Python. Familiar with many other object-oriented languages.